

EDUCATION

Dalian University of Technology

Apr 2010 - Feb 2015

Bachelor's Degree of Mathematics and Computer Science.

PING ZHAO

Senior Software Engineer

PROFILE

I am a Senior Software Engineer with 8 years of hands-on experience, and very confident in my technical skills, experience, team work ability, and communication skills. I have worked in several companies in the United States, Canada, the United Kingdom, and France as a remote developer and Team Lead. I have rich experience in Startup Companies and very familiar with Agile Methodology.

CONTACT

PHONE:

136 2498 1040

WEBSITE:

https://zhaoping-portfolio.herokuapp.com

EMAIL:

zhaoping.dev@gmail.com

SKYPE:

live:.cid.b7ea3e4ceb1b7f07

WORK EXPERIENCE

Divergence Neuro – Senior Frontend Engineer

Mar 2021-Oct 2021

Built frontend of <u>Divergence Neuro Platform</u> using React/Redux with Typescript.

5loyalty - Full-stack Engineer

Jun 2021-Aug 2021

Take part in building Online Ordering App using React, Ionic, Django, and Firebase. (<u>Kauai App</u>, <u>Pure App</u>)

Work Well Together - Full-stack Engineer

Built WWT App alone using React, Django, AWS (WWT APP)

Collins Harper – Frontend Developer

Mar 2020-Jul 2020

Take part in building Ecommerce website using React, Node.js, Vue.js, Magento, AWS. (<u>Image 3D</u>)

KR Soft - Team Lead & Software Engineer

Nov 2016-Mar 2020

Take part in building number of websites and mobile apps (Recognize App, Racing Manager)

SKILLS

Frontend: React, Next.js, Vue.js, React Native, Ionic, Redux, Solid.js, Svelte, Nuxt.js, Angular, Gatsby

Backend: Django, Node.js, Express, Nest.js, Laravel,

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Others: AWS, GCP, Docker, Firebase, CI/CD, Mathematics, Machine Learning, Data Science, Algorithm